AI Research Chatbot

AI Research Chatbot is a Streamlit app that allows users to search and summarize computer science papers from the ArXiv dataset. Users can search by keywords, view paper abstracts, and get summarized versions of the content.

Features:

1.Loads the ArXiv metadata dataset.
2.Search papers by title or abstract.
3.Summarizes paper abstracts using a transformer model.

Requirements:
1.Install dependencies:
pip install streamlit pandas transformers

2.Download the ArXiv metadata JSON file and update its path in the load_data() function.


Key Functions:

1.load_data(): Loads the dataset and filters computer science papers.
2.summarize_paper(): Summarizes abstracts using a Hugging Face model.
3.search_papers(): Searches papers based on keywords.


Run the file by streamlit